Guide to the Stanford Channel Master Videorecordings
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Videos (Box 1)
  - InterChange
    - Interview with Harry Elam, 99-753 (Box 78)
    - Theodore Glasser, 99-754 (Box 78)
    - Interview with Mark Zoback, 99-755 (Box 78)
    - Interview with Terry Winograd, 99-756 (Box 78)
    - Interview with David Kennedy, 99-757 (Box 78)
    - Luis Fraga, 99-758 (Box 78)
    - Jeffrey Pfeffer, 99-759 (Box 78)
    - Conversation with Eavan Boland, 00-762 (Box 79)
    - Conversation with Albert Camarillo, 00-763 (Box 79)
    - Interview with William Gould, 00-764 (Box 79)
    - Interview with Kathryn Moler, 00-765 (Box 79)
    - Interview with Susan Okin, 00-770 (Box 79)
    - Condoleezza Rice, 99-760 (Box 79)
    - Karla Lemon, 99-761 (Box 79)
    - A Conversation with Robert Sutton, 00-766 (Box 79)
    - Conversation with Wanda Corn, 00-767 (Box 79)
    - Conversation with Robert Joss, 00-768 (Box 79)
    - Conversation with Richard White, 00-769 (Box 79)
  - REEL VISIONS
    - Program #1, 95-801 (Box 80)
    - Program #2, 95-802 (Box 80)
    - Program #3, 95-803 (Box 80)
    - Program #4, 95-804 (Box 80)
    - Program #5, 95-805 (Box 80)
    - Program #6, 95-806 (Box 80)
    - Program #7, 95-807 (Box 80)
    - Program #8, 95-808 (Box 80)
    - Program #9, 95-809 (Box 80)
    - Program #10, 95-810 (Box 80)
    - Program #11, 95-811 (Box 80)
    - Program #12, 95-812 (Box 81)
    - Program #13, 96-813 (Box 81)
    - Program #14, 96-814 (Box 81)
    - Program #15, 96-815 (Box 81)
    - Program #16, 96-816 (Box 81)
    - Program #17, 96-817 (Box 81)
    - Program #18, 96-818 (Box 81)
    - Program #19, 96-819 (Box 81)
    - Program #20, 96-820 (Box 81)
    - Program #21, 96-821 (Box 81)
    - Program #22, 96-822 (Box 81)
    - Program #23, 96-823 (Box 82)
    - Program #24, 96-824 (Box 82)
    - "Program #25", 96-825 (Box 82)
    - Program #26, 96-826 (Box 82)
    - Program #27, 96-827 (Box 82)
    - Program #28, 98-828 (Box 83)
    - Program #38: Interconnection, 00-841 (Box 84)
    - Program #39: Reflections, 00-842 (Box 84)
    - Program #29, 98-829 (Box 84)
    - Program #30, 98-830 (Box 84)
    - Program #31, 98-831 (Box 84)
    - Program #32, 98-832 (Box 84)
    - Program # 33, 98-833 (Box 84)
    - Program # 34, 98-834 (Box 84)
    - Program #35, 98-835 (Box 84)
    - Program # 36, 98-836 (Box 84)
    - Program #37, 98-837 (Box 84)
  - Media Technologies, People and Society
    - Course Introduction, 97-828 (Box 82)
    - What is Communication?, 97-829 (Box 82)
    - Modality, 97-830 (Box 82)
    - Interactivity, 97-831 (Box 82)
    - The Notion of Reality in the Media, 97-832 (Box 82)
    - Social Reality and Virtual Communities, 97-833 (Box 82)
    - Social Responses to Communication Technology, 97-834 (Box 83)
    - Concept of Interface Design, 97-835 (Box 83)
    - Consumer Behavior and Persuasion, 97-836 (Box 83)
    - Advertising: Subliminal and Conscious Messages, 97-837 (Box 83)
    - Attention and Memory, 97-838 (Box 83)
    - Emotion and Arousal, 97-839 (Box 83)
    - New Media and Public Policy, 97-840 (Box 83)
    - Violence, Pornography and Erotica, 97-841 (Box 83)
    - Reactions to Technology; Can Computers Have Personalities?, 97-842 (Box 83)
    - Conceptions of Technology and Research, 97-843 (Box 83)
  - Health and Society
    - Why Zebras Don't Get Ulcers, 95-901 (Box 84)
    - Sleep Disorders, 95-902 (Box 84)
    - Great American Health Controversies: Medical Practices of East and West, 95-904 (Box 85)
    - Decisions at the End of Life: Withholding and Withdrawing Life Support, 95-905 (Box 85)
    - Patients and Caregivers: Building Authentic Relationships, 96-906 (Box 85)
    - Medicare and Managed Care, 96-907 (Box 85)
    - Great American Health Controversies: The Mind-Body Connection, 96-908 (Box 85)
    - Great American Health Controversies: Hormone Replacement Therapy, 96-909 (Box 85)
    - Teenage Sexuality, 96-910 (Box 85)
    - History and Hysterics: What About the Future?, 96-911 (Box 85)
    - Life Begins at 40, 96-912 (Box 85)
    - Re-Defining Professional Ethics in the Age of Managed Care, 96-913 (Box 85)
    - Biology of Sexual Orientation, 97-914 (Box 85)
    - Cancer as a Turning Point: From Surviving to Thriving, Part 1 tape #1, 97-915 (Box 86)
    - Cancer as a Turning Point: From Surviving to Thriving, Part 1, 97-915 (Box 86)
    - Cancer as a Turning Point: From Surviving to Thriving, Part 2 tape #1, 97-916 (Box 86)
    - Cancer as a Turning Point: From Surviving to Thriving, Part 2, 97-916 (Box 86)
    - Cancer as a Turning Point: From Surviving to Thriving, Part 3, 97-917 (Box 86)
    - Changing Who We Are: Prozac, Ritalin and the American Family, Part 1 tape #1, 97-918 (Box 86)
    - Changing Who We Are: Prozac, Ritalin and the American Family, Part 1, 97-918 (Box 86)
    - Changing Who We Are: Prozac, Ritalin and the American Family, Part 2, 97-919 (Box 86)
    - History of Heart Transplantation, 97-920 (Box 86)
    - Trauma and Memory, 97-921 (Box 86)
    - Stress and Coping: What Baboons Can Teach Us, 97-922 (Box 86)
    - Ethnicity in Medicine, Part 1: Health and Communication: The Effective Use of Interpreter Skills Across Cultures, 97-923 (Box 86)
    - Ethnicity in Medicine, Part 2: Education, Substance Abuse, Mental Health, and Other Determinants of Violence in Minority Communities, 97-924 (Box 86)
    - Ethnicity in Medicine, Part 3: Culture, End of Life and Bioethics: What Differences Make a Difference?, 97-925 (Box 86)
    - Ethnicity in Medicine, Part 4: Alternative Medicine and Therapeutic Relationship: Cultural Awareness, Sensitivity and Respect, 97-926 (Box 87)
    - Healing Circles: Choices for Back Pain, 97-927 (Box 87)
    - Healing Circles: Choices for Arthritis, 97-928 (Box 87)
    - The Cholesterol Myth, 97-929 (Box 87)
    - With a Little Help From My Friends: Effects of Support Groups for Cancer Patients, 97-930 (Box 87)
    - Adult Development: The Time of Your Life, 97-931 (Box 87)
    - The Battle Over Managed Care in California, 97-932 (Box 87)
    - Parenting in the '90s, 97-933 (Box 87)
    - Death and the Doctor: The Final Step in the Art of Healing, 97-934 (Box 87)
    - Genetic Testing and Alzheimer's Disease: Has the Time Come? Part 1 tape #1, 97-935/a (Box 87)
    - Genetic Testing and Alzheimer's Disease: Has the Time Come? Part 1, 97-935/a (Box 87)
    - Genetic Testing and Alzheimer's Disease: Has The Time Come? Part 2 tape #1, 97-935/b (Box 87)
    - Genetic Testing and Alzheimer's Disease: Has The Time Come? Part 2, 97-935/b (Box 87)
    - Genetic Testing and Alzheimer's Testing: Has the Time Come? Part 3 tape #1, 97-935/c (Box 88)
    - Genetic Testing and Alzheimer's Testing: Has the Time Come? Part 3, 97-935/c (Box 88)
    - Reclaiming the Satisfaction and Meaning of Our Work in Health Care, 97-936 (Box 88)
    - Prevention and Treatment of Cancer of the Prostate, 97-937 (Box 88)
    - A Symposium for Mothers: The Delicate Balance, 98-938 (Box 88)
    - When Your Patient Asks About Alternative Medicine, Pt 1, 98-939/a (Box 88)
    - When Your Patient Asks About Alternative Medicine, Pt 2 tape #1, 98-939/b (Box 88)
    - When Your Patient Asks About Alternative Medicine, Pt 2 tape #2, 98-939/b (Box 88)
    - When Your Patient Asks About Alternative Medicine, Pt 3 tape #1, 98-939/c (Box 88)
    - When Your Patient Asks About Alternative Medicine, Pt 3 tape #2, 98-939/c (Box 88)
    - Ethnogeriatrics and Managed Care: The Rewards and Challenges of Cultural Competence, Part 1, 98-940/a (Box 88)
    - Ethnogeriatrics and Managed Care: The Rewards and Challenges of Cultural Competence, Part 2, 98-940/b (Box 88)
    - Great American Health Controversies: Sports in America tape #1, 98-941 (Box 89)
    - Great American Health Controversies: Sports in America tape #2, 98-941 (Box 89)
    - Understanding Manic-Depression and Bipolar Disorders, 98-942 (Box 89)
    - Transforming the Culture of Death in America, 98-943 (Box 89)
    - Individual Genetic Variation: Implications of the Coming Transformation of Medicine tape #1, 98-944/a (Box 89)
    - Individual Genetic Variation: Implications of the Coming Transformation of Medicine tape #2, 98-944/a (Box 89)
    - Individual Genetic Variation: Implications of the Coming Transformation of Medicine. tape #1, 98-944/b (Box 89)
    - Individual Genetic Variation: Implications of the Coming Transformation of Medicine. tape #2, 98-944/b (Box 89)
    - Individual Genetic Variation: Implications of the Coming Transformation of Medicine tape #1, 98-944/c (Box 89)
    - Individual Genetic Variation: Implications of the Coming Transformation of Medicine tape #2, 98-944/c (Box 89)
    - Individual Genetic Variation: Implications of the Coming Transformation of Medicine, 98-944/d (Box 89)
    - Breast Cancer: New Directions in Prevention, Diagnosis and Treatment, 98-945 (Box 89)
    - Complementary Medicine at Stanford, 98-946 (Box 89)
    - Aging in the New Millenium, 98-947 (Box 89)
    - Phytonutrients and Anti-oxidants: The Myths and Realities About Their Role in Cancer, 98-948 (Box 89)
    - Male Erectile Dysfunction: Diagnosis and New Treatment Options, 98-949 (Box 90)
    - New Developments in the Treatment of Coronary Heart Disease: Angiogenesis, 99-950 (Box 90)
    - Stress Management and Your Health, 99-951 (Box 90)
    - Symposium for Mothers: Finding Balance in a Hurried World, 99-952 (Box 90)
    - Women's Cancers, 99-953 (Box 90)
    - Spirituality, Religion and Healing, 99-954 (Box 90)
    - Type II Diabetes: Evidence That Treatment Can Be Beneficial, 99-955 (Box 90)
    - Helping Your Child, 99-956 (Box 90)
    - New Frontiers in Interventional Cardiology, 99-957 (Box 90)
    - Spirituality and Aging: Spiritual and Ethical Concerns in the Care of Older Patients, 99-958/a (Box 90)
    - Spirituality and Aging: Insights and Clinical Applications, 99-958/b (Box 90)
    - Spirituality and Aging: Insights and Clinical Applications tape #1, 99-958/c (Box 91)
    - Spirituality and Aging: Insights and Clinical Applications tape #2, 99-958/c (Box 91)
    - Having Trouble Sleeping?, 99-959 (Box 91)
    - Demystifying Infertility tape #1, 99-960 (Box 91)
    - Demystifying Infertility tape #2, 99-960 (Box 91)
    - Alternative Medicine at Stanford: An Update, 99-961 (Box 91)
    - The Hand That Built the Brain: Lucy Sends a Message to the Cognitive Scientists, 99-962 (Box 91)
    - New Treatment Options for Lower Back Pain, 99-963 (Box 91)
    - Got a Grudge: The Art and Science of Forgiveness, 99-964 (Box 91)
    - Jonathan King Lecture:Doctor, Doctor, Lend Me Your Ear, 99-965 (Box 91)
    - When it Comes to Cancer, It's All in the Genes, 99-966 (Box 91)
    - Medications for Pain Management: Opportunities and Perspectives, 99-967 (Box 91)
    - Practical Geriatrics: Challenges and Rewards, 99-968/a (Box 91)
    - From Moles to Melanoma: Advances in Screening and Staging, 00-969 (Box 92)
    - Health Care Forecasts for the 21st Century, 00-970 (Box 92)
    - Weight Loss: Losing Fat to Become Lean and Healthy, 00-971 (Box 92)
    - Poetic Medicine: The Healing Art of Poem-Making, 00-972 (Box 92)
    - A Symposium for Mothers: Once a Mother, Always a Mother: Caring Across the Generations, 00-973/a (Box 92)
    - A Symposium for Mothers: Once a Mother, Always a Mother: Caring Across the Generations, 00-973/b (Box 92)
    - Practical Geriatrics: Challenges and Rewards, 99-968/b (Box 92)
    - Practical Geriatrics: Challenges and Rewards, 99-968/c (Box 92)
    - Practical Geriatrics: Challenges and Rewards, 99-968/d (Box 92)
    - Practical Geriatrics: Challenges and Rewards, 99-968/e (Box 92)
    - Cancer and the Immune System, 00-974 (Box 93)
    - Management of HIV: An Update, 00-975/a (Box 93)
    - Management of HIV: An Update, 00-975/b (Box 93)
    - Management of HIV: An Update tape #1, 00-975/c (Box 93)
    - Management of HIV: An Update tape #2, 00-975/c (Box 93)
    - Osteoporosis and Arthritis: Physical Activity and a Healthy Skeleton, 00-976 (Box 93)
    - Long Term Care for You or Your Loved One, 00-977 (Box 93)
    - Headaches: A Complementary Non-Drug Approach, 00-978 (Box 93)
    - Stanford Restart Cardiology Program, 00-979 (Box 93)
    - The Ethnogeriatric Imperative and Its Implications, 00-980 (Box 93)
    - Betrayal of Trust: The Collapse of Global Public Health, 00-981 (Box 93)
    - Incorporating Quality of Life into Health Policy Decisions: A Gerontologic Issue, 00-982 (Box 93)
    - 2000 Jonathan J. King Lecture: Living in the Bonus Round: A Performance by Steve Schalchlin, 00-983 (Box 94)
    - Syndrome X: Over-Coming the Silent Killer That Can Cause Heart Attacks tape #1, 00-984 (Box 94)
    - Syndrome X: Over-Coming the Silent Killer That Can Cause Heart Attacks tape #2, 00-984 (Box 94)
    - When to Pull the Plug: The Intensive Care Dilemma, 00-985 (Box 94)
    - The Effects of Spiritual and Religious Practices on Cardiovascular Disease, 00-986 (Box 94)
    - Practical Geriatrics: Adapting and Implementing Practice Geriatrics, 00-987/a (Box 94)
    - Practical Geriatrics: Lessons from Research, Lessons from Experience, 00-987/b (Box 94)
    - Practical Geriatrics: Lessons from Research, Lessons from Experience, 00-987/c (Box 94)
    - Practical Geriatrics: Lessons from Research, Lessons from Experience, 00-987/d (Box 94)
    - Practical Geriatrics: Lessons from Research, Lessons fromExperience, 00-987/e (Box 94)
    - Practical Geriatrics: Lessons from Research, Lessons from Experience, 00-987/f (Box 94)
    - Practical Geriatrics: Lessons from Research, Lessons from Experience, 00-987/g (Box 94)
    - Hybrids and Cyborgs: Melding Medicine and the Humanities: The Doctor as Writer, 01-988 (Box 95)
    - The Fourth Annual Symposium for Mothers presents "Embrace the Challenge: Finding Calm Amid the Stress Reclaiming Family Lifein the Bay Area Part One: Welcoming Remarks and a Talk by Dee Brummett, Principal of La Entrada School., 01-989/a (Box 95)
    - Finding Calm Amid the Stress: Reclaiming Family Life in the Bay Area, 01-989/b (Box 95)
    - The Fourth Annual Symposium for Mothers presents "Embrace the Challenge: "Finding Calm Amid the Stress Reclaiming Family Lifein the Bay Area Part Three: Panel Insights and Sharing", 01-989/c (Box 95)
    - Hybrids and Cyborgs: Voices in the Gallery and A Strong Dose of Myself, 01-990 (Box 95)
    - Opening Your Heart: Anatomically, Emotionally, and Spiritually, 01-991 (Box 95)
    - The Wisdom Project: "Spirituality at the Bedside: Views of an M.D.-Chaplain.", 01-992/a (Box 95)
    - The Wisdom Project: "A Necessary Dialogue" Betsy Carpenter, 01-992/b (Box 95)
    - The Wisdom Project: "In the ICU, Time is Relative (Einstein was Right!)" Ernle Young, 01-992/c (Box 95)
    - The Wisdom Project: "Right to Die: Right to Choose?", 01-992/d (Box 95)
    - The Wisdom Project: "Detoxifying Death" David Spiegel, 01-992/e (Box 95)
    - Brain Tumors, Diagnosis and Treatment, 01-993 (Box 96)
    - The Narrative of Exposure: Confluences of Literature and Medicine, 01-994 (Box 96)
  - International Security in a Changing World
    - Class #1: Course Introduction, 00-1001 (Box 96)
    - Class #2: The Past and Future of International Security, 00-1002 (Box 96)
    - Deterrence in Theory and Practice, 00-1003 (Box 96)
    - Class #4: Theory and Practice of Arms Control, 00-1004 (Box 96)
    - Class #5: The Role of the United Nations in Disarmament, 00-1005 (Box 96)
    - Class #6: Making a Nuclear Bomb, 00-1006 (Box 96)
    - Class #7: The Biological Weapons Threat, 00-1007 (Box 96)
    - Class #8: Nuclear Responses to Chemical and Biological Weapons, 00-1008 (Box 96)
    - Class #9: The Ballistic Missile Defense Debate, 00-1009 (Box 96)
    - Class #10: Cooperative Threat Reduction, 00-1010 (Box 97)
    - Class #11: Terrorist Threats from the Soviet Nuclear Legacy, 00-1011 (Box 97)
    - Class #12: The Nonproliferation Regime, 00-1012 (Box 97)
    - Class #13: The NPT Review Conference, 00-1013 (Box 97)
    - Class #14: U.S. Decisions to Intervene, 00-1014 (Box 97)
    - Class #15: Preventing Civil Wars, 00-1015 (Box 97)
    - Class #16: Ending Civil Wars, 00-1016 (Box 97)
    - Class #17: Case Study: Kashmir, 00-1017 (Box 97)
    - Class #18: Case Study: Chechnya, 00-1018 (Box 97)
    - Class #19: Causes and Consequences of Internal Wars, 00-1019 (Box 97)
    - Class #20: Great Power Rivalries: Past as Prologue?, 00-1020 (Box 97)
    - Class #21: The Russian Dilemma, 00-1021 (Box 98)
    - Class #22: The Future of China, 00-1022 (Box 98)
    - Class #23: Germany and Japan, 00-1023 (Box 98)
    - Class #24: Developing Countries as Emerging Great Powers?, 00-1024 (Box 98)
    - Class #25: The Revolution in Military Affairs and the Future Battlefield, 00-1025 (Box 98)
    - Class #26: Energy and Security, 00-1026 (Box 98)
    - Class #27: Reflections on the Future, 00-1027 (Box 98)
  - International Environmental Politics
    - Class #1: Introduction, 01-1030 (Box 98)
    - Class #2: Evaluating Policy Impacts, 01-1031 (Box 98)
    - Class #3: A Scientific Perspective, 01-1032 (Box 98)
    - Class #4: An Ecophilosophical Perspective and a Political Perspective, 01-1033 (Box 98)
    - Class #5: An Economic Perspective and a Legal Perspective, 01-1034 (Box 99)
    - Class #6: Nonstate Actors: Nongovernmental Organizations and Multinational Corporations, 01-1035 (Box 99)
    - Class #7: How to Conduct a Good Causal Evaluation of a Treaty's Influence, 01-1036 (Box 99)
    - Class #8: Problem Identification Theory, 01-1037 (Box 99)
    - Class #9: Negotiation Theory, 01-1038 (Box 99)
    - Class #10: Compliance Theory, 01-1039 (Box 99)
    - Class #11: Relative Regime Effectiveness: Whaling and Ozone Protection, 01-1040 (Box 99)
    - Class #12: Environment and Security, 01-1041 (Box 99)
    - Class #13: Sustainable Development-Guest Lecture by Karen Seto (Center for Environmental Science and Policy), 01-1042 (Box 99)
    - Class #14: Free Trade and Environment, 01-1043 (Box 99)
    - Class #15: World Bank and Environmental Protection, 01-1044 (Box 99)
    - Class #16: Population, 01-1045 (Box 100)
    - Class #17: Student Presentations of Research Paper Findings, 01-1046 (Box 100)
    - Class #18: Debrief of Climate Change Simulation, 01-1047 (Box 100)
    - Class #19: The Future of Global Environmental Governance, 01-1048 (Box 100)
  - Uncommon Knowledge
    - National Drug Policies, 96-1107 (Box 100)
    - On Congress, 96-1108 (Box 100)
    - George Shultz on China, 96-1109 (Box 100)
    - School Choice, 96-1110 (Box 100)
    - Nuclear Proliferation with Drell & Teller, 96-1111 (Box 101)
    - Affirmative Action with Shelby Steele, 96-1112 (Box 101)
    - George Shultz on Bosnia, 96-1113 (Box 101)
    - Migrations and Cultures with Thomas Sowell, 96-1114 (Box 101)
    - Migrations and Cultures with Thomas Sowell, 96-1114 (Box 101)
    - Russia with Malia and Dunlop, 96-1115 (Box 101)
    - Middle East w/ Hill and Sofaer, 96-1116 (Box 101)
    - Seymour Martin Lipset, 96-1117 (Box 101)
    - On Politics with Brady and Rivers, 96-1118 (Box 101)
    - United Nations, 96-1119 (Box 101)
    - Red Flag Over Hong Kong, 96-1122 (Box 101)
    - Deficit Disorder, 97-1120 (Box 101)
    - Aging: From Baby Boom to Bust, 97-1121 (Box 101)
    - The Rich Get Richer, 97-1123 (Box 101)
    - One Percent Solution?, 97-1124 (Box 101)
    - Reading, Writing, Reform, 97-1125 (Box 101)
    - "Fundamentally" Speaking, 97-1126 (Box 101)
    - Point, Click....Censorship, 97-1127 (Box 101)
    - Political Tectonics, 97-1128 (Box 101)
    - Farewell, Welfare, 97-1129 (Box 101)
    - Lock 'Em Up?, 97-1130 (Box 101)
    - The British Elections, 97-1131 (Box 101)
    - Brave New World Order, 97-1132 (Box 101)
    - On Guard, 98-1133 (Box 101)
    - National Insecurity, 98-1134 (Box 101)
    - Hear No English, Speak No English, 98-1135 (Box 101)
    - This Land is My Land, 98-1136 (Box 101)
    - Cybersnoops, 98-1137 (Box 101)
    - Gen X Files, 98-1138 (Box 101)
    - They're Coming to America, 98-1139 (Box 101)
    - Curtains for Windows?, 98-1140 (Box 101)
    - Red Tide Rising, 98-1141 (Box 101)
    - Lost in Space?, 98-1142 (Box 101)
    - Follow the Money, 98-1143 (Box 101)
    - The Heat Is On, 98-1144 (Box 101)
    - A House Divided, 98-1145 (Box 101)
    - Up In Smoke: The War on Tobacco, 98-1146 (Box 101)
    - Making the Grade: Charter Schools, 00-1100 (Box 102)
    - Corporate U: Corporate Funding of Academic Research, 00-1101 (Box 102)
    - Peeping Coms: Internet Privacy, 00-1102 (Box 102)
    - Colombian (White) Powder Keg: U.S. Aid to Colombia, 00-1103 (Box 102)
    - Whose Genes? Patenting the Human Genome, 00-1104 (Box 102)
    - A Crack In the Ice: The Legacy of the Reykjavik Summit, 00-1105 (Box 102)
    - Turn Out the Lights, The Party's Over: Why Socialism Didn't Happen in the United States, 00-1106 (Box 102)
    - Don't Stop Thinking About Tomorrow: The Clinton Legacy, 00-1107 (Box 102)
    - Patent on the Fritz: Patenting the Internet Economy, 00-1108 (Box 102)
    - The Battle for Britain: Britain and the European Union, 00-1109 (Box 102)
    - Nowhere to Run, Nowhere to Hide: Bioterrorism, 98-1147 (Box 102)
    - It's All Foreign to Me: Clinton Administration Foreign Policy, 98-1148 (Box 102)
    - Show Me the Money: The Minimum Wage Debate, 98-1149 (Box 102)
    - Media Circus: The State of the Media, 98-1150 (Box 102)
    - Jury on Trial: Reforming the Criminal Justice System, 98-1151 (Box 102)
    - Playing Hardball: The Best Way to Fight and Deter Crime, 98-1152 (Box 102)
    - It Ain't Over Til It's Over: U.S.-Russia Relations After the Cold War, 98-1153 (Box 102)
    - Dee-Fense: Ballistic Missile Defense, 98-1154 (Box 102)
    - Dee-Fense: Ballistic Missile Defense, 98-1154 (Box 102)
    - Semper Fidel? The Cuban Embargo, 98-1155 (Box 102)
    - History in the Streets: 1968 and the Counterculture, 98-1156 (Box 102)
    - You Said You Wanted a Revolution: 1968 and the Counter-Counterculture, 98-1157 (Box 102)
    - Social Insecurity: Reforming Social Security, 98-1158 (Box 102)
    - Peace by Piece: The Israeli-Palestinian Peace Process, 98-1159 (Box 102)
    - Farewell to Arms? Gun Control, 98-1160 (Box 102)
    - School Rivalry: Education Reform, 98-1161 (Box 102)
    - Census and Sensibility: Population and Resources, 98-1162 (Box 102)
    - Chained to the Past: Race and Integration, 98-1163 (Box 102)
    - Greening of American Foreign Policy, 98-1164 (Box 102)
    - International Monetary Fund, 98-1165 (Box 102)
    - American Politics in the Year 2000, 98-1166 (Box 102)
    - Veto NATO? The Future of NATO, 98-1167 (Box 102)
    - A Motion to Dismiss: The Independent Counsel Statute, 99-1168 (Box 102)
    - What Does It Mean to be a Libertarian?, 99-1169 (Box 102)
    - Milton Friedman Meets the President, 99-1170 (Box 102)
    - Doing Time and Making Profits: The Privatization of Prisons, 99-1171 (Box 102)
    - How Greedy Is My Valley? Techno-libertarians in Silicon Valley, 00-1110 (Box 103)
    - Up In Arms Overs the Second Amendment: Meaning of the Second Amendment, 00-1111 (Box 103)
    - Elephants On Parade: Conservatism in Modern America, 00-1112 (Box 103)
    - What's Hate Got To Do With It? Hate Crimes Legislation, 00-1172 (Box 103)
    - They've Paved Paradise and Put Up a Parking Lot: Urban Sprawl, 00-1173 (Box 103)
    - You've Come a Long Way, Maybe: Feminism Today, 00-1174 (Box 103)
    - Field of Genes: Genetically Modified Foods, 00-1175 (Box 103)
    - A Bug's Life: A Conversation with Tom Wolfe, 00-1176 (Box 103)
    - NYPD Blues: Fighting Crime in New York City, 00-1177 (Box 103)
    - Forts and Firebreaks: America's International Military Commitment, 00-1178 (Box 103)
    - Wiring for Dollars: Electronic Money Revolution, 00-1179 (Box 103)
    - Doctoring the System: Health Care Reform, 00-1180 (Box 103)
    - Chip Off the Old Bloc: Lessons of Kosovo, 00-1181 (Box 103)